kemifilani.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy - Kemi Filani News

**Privacy Policy** for http://kemifilani.com

The privacy of our visitors to http://kemifilani.com is important to us.

At http://kemifilani.com,  
we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.  
Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and  
collect when you use and visit http://kemifilani.com, and how we  
safeguard your information. **We never sell your personal information to third parties**.

 **Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in  
log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet  
protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or  
Globacom Nigeria), the browser you used to visit our site (such as  
Internet Explorer, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and  
which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
This blog use cookies and some of our business partners  
(for example, advertisers) use cookies and web beacons when they  
advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as  
Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP  
address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some  
cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally **used for geotargeting purposes**  
(showing Lagos Real Estate ads to someone in Lagos, Nigeria, for  
example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as  
showing mobile phones ads to someone who frequents Phone sites).

This site has no access to, or control of advertisers’ cookies.

 **DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s  
DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are  
browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising  
(including some Google AdSense advertisements).

This  
cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests  
(”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on  
your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing  
sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel  
advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about  
hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. **It does NOT track personal information about you** ,  
such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number,  
social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  
You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising  
by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You  
can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or  
third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences  
in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect  
how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  
This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such  
as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies  
does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  
Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a  
site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by [KemiFilani](http://kemifilani.com/)
